

Aleksandar Mihaljev

Mechatronics Engineer

□ amihaljev91@gmail.com

****+38164/9173620

Highly motivated Mechatronics engineer in pursuit of gaining new knowledge and experiences in programming and software development. I am ambitious, hardworking and want to find a company that I can grow with as I achieve their goals.

Experience

Meridian doo. Operater

March 2020 - Present

A/N Group

Intern

Sep 2015 - Dec 2015

Technologies: PLC and SCADA

Working in team responsible for implementing innovative automation industry solutions. From architecture, detail design to coding and testing.

Education

Faculty of Technical Science, University of Novi Sad Bachelors of Science in Mechatronics, Robotics and Engineering 2010 - 2020

Skills

- C
- PLC
- SCADA

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript

Personal Skills

- Driving license B
- Mother language: Serbian
- Other languages: English and German
- Adaptable
- Team Player
- Organized